Guide to the John L. Hennessy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0700
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 2000 Sep 1-2016 Aug 31; Accession ARCH-2016-117
  - 4/2/2006 - 4/28/2006 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 5/2/2006 - 5/31/2006 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 5/2/2006 - 5/31/2006 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 6/1/2006 - 6/26/2006 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 6/2/2006 - 6/20/2006 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 7/3/2006 - 7/26/2006 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 7/5/2006 - 7/31/2006 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 8/1/2006 - 8/30/2006 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 8/1/2006 - 8/24/2006 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 9/1/2006 - 9/28/2006 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 9/5/2006 - 9/29/2006 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 10/5/2006 - 10/31/2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 10/3/2006 - 10/31/2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 11/1/2006 - 11/29/2006 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 11/1/2006 - 11/30/2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 12/1/2006 - 12/19/2006 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 12/1/2006 - 12/18/2006 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1/2/2007 - 1/31/2007 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1/3/2007 - 1/31/2007 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 2/1/2007 - 2/28/2007 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 2/1/2007 - 2/27/2007 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 3/1/2007 - 3/23/2007 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 3/1/2007 - 3/23/2007 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 4/1/2007 - 4/30/2007 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 4/2/2007 - 4/30/2007 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 5/1/2007 - 5/31/2007 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 5/1/2007 - 5/31/2007 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 6/1/2007 - 6/27/2007 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 6/1/2007 - 6/21/2007 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 7/1/2007 - 7/31/2007 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 7/9/2007 - 7/27/2007 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 8/13/2007 - 8/30/2007 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 8/6/2007 - 8/31/2007 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 9/1/2007 - 9/28/2007 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 9/11/2007 - 9/28/2007 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 10/1/2007 - 10/30/2007 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 10/1/2007 - 10/31/2007 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 11/1/2007 - 11/30/2007 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 11/1/2007 - 11/30/2007 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 12/1/2007 - 12/19/2007 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 12/3/2007 - 12/12/2007 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1/7/2008 - 1/28/2008 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1/3/2008 - 1/31/2008 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 2/1/2008 - 2/28/2008 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 2/1/2008 - 2/29/2008 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 3/1/2008 - 3/24/2008 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 3/3/2008 - 3/21/2008 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 4/1/2008 - 4/29/2008 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 4/3/2008 - 4/25/2008 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 5/1/2008 - 5/29/2008 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 5/1/2008 - 5/30/2008 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 6/1/2008 - 6/30/2008 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 6/2/2008 - 6/17/2008 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 7/1/2008 - 7/26/2008 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 7/8/2008 - 7/24/2008 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 8/1/2008 - 8/27/2008 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 8/5/2008 - 8/26/2008 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 9/1/2008 - 9/30/2008 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 9/9/2008 - 9/30/2008 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 10/1/2008 - 10/31/2008 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 10/1/2008 - 10/31/2008 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 11/1/2008 - 11/24/2008 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 11/3/2008 - 11/26/2008 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 12/1/2008 - 12/18/2008 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 12/2/2008 - 12/18/2008 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 1/1/2009 - 1/26/2009 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1/9/2009 - 1/27/2009 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 2/1/2009 - 2/27/2009 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 2/2/2009 - 2/27/2009 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 3/2/2009 - 3/30/2009 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 3/3/2009 - 3/31/2009 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 4/1/2009 - 4/28/2009 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 4/2/2009 - 4/30/2009 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 5/1/2009 - 5/29/2009 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 5/1/2009 - 5/29/2009 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 6/1/2009 - 6/30/2009 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 6/2/2009 - 6/30/2009 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 7/13/2009 - 7/23/2009 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 7/6/2009 - 7/22/2009 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 8/10/2009 - 8/28/2009 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 8/11/2009 - 8/26/2009 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 9/1/2009 - 9/30/2009 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - 9/8/2009 - 9/30/2009 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - 10/1/2009 - 10/29/2009 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - 10/5/2009 - 10/30/2009 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - 11/1/2009 - 11/30/2009 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - 11/2/2009 - 11/20/2009 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - 12/4/2009 - 12/18/2009 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 12/2/2009 - 12/15/2009 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 1/1/2010 - 1/21/2010 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 1/4/2010 - 1/19/2010 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 2/3/2010 - 2/26/2010 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 2/3/2010 - 2/26/2010 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 3/1/2010 - 3/30/2010 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 3/1/2010 - 3/31/2010 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 4/1/2010 - 4/26/2010 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 4/2/2010 - 4/22/2010 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 5/1/2010 - 5/25/2010 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 5/6/2010 - 5/27/2010 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 6/1/2010 - 6/24/2010 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 6/1/2010 - 6/29/2010 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 7/6/2010 - 7/19/2010 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 7/15/2010 - 7/19/2010 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 8/1/2010 - 8/27/2010 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - 8/5/2010 - 8/26/2010 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - 9/1/2010 - 9/30/2010 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - 9/13/2010 - 9/30/2010 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - 10/4/2010 - 10/28/2010 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - 10/1/2010 - 10/28/2010 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - 11/1/2010 - 11/30/2010 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 11/8/2010 - 11/30/2010 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 12/1/2010 - 12/31/2010 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 12/1/2010 - 12/16/2010 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 1/1/2011 - 1/31/2011 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1/5/2011 - 1/31/2011 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 2/1/2011 - 2/28/2011 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 2/1/2011 - 2/25/2011 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 3/1/2011 - 3/30/2011 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 3/1/2011 - 3/31/2011 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 4/5/2011 - 4/25/2011 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 4/1/2011 - 4/29/2011 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 5/1/2011 - 5/31/2011 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 5/2/2011 - 5/31/2011 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 6/1/2011 - 6/28/2011 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 6/1/2011 - 6/20/2011 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 7/1/2011 - 7/26/2011 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - 7/11/2011 - 7/25/2011 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - 8/2/2011 - 8/31/2011 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - 8/3/2011 - 8/25/2011 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - 9/7/2011 - 9/28/2011 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 9/9/2011 - 9/30/2011 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - 10/11/2011 - 10/31/2011 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - 10/6/2011 - 10/14/2011 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - 11/1/2011 - 11/29/2011 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 11/1/2011 - 11/29/2011 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 12/1/2011 - 12/15/2011 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 12/5/2011 - 12/12/2011 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1/9/2012 - 1/31/2012 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 1/18/2012 - 1/31/2012 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 2/1/2012 - 2/29/2012 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 2/2/2012 - 2/27/2012 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 3/1/2012 - 3/28/2012 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 3/5/2012 - 3/26/2012 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 4/2/2012 - 4/30/2012 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 4/2/2012 - 4/30/2012 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 5/1/2012 - 5/30/2012 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 5/7/2012 - 5/21/2012 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 6/1/2012 - 6/15/2012 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 6/4/2012 - 6/11/2012 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 7/2/2012 - 7/26/2012 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 7/25/2012 - 7/31/2012 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - 8/8/2012 - 8/31/2012 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - 8/1/2012 - 8/30/2012 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - 9/1/2012 - 9/25/2012 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - 9/4/2012 - 9/25/2012 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - 10/1/2012 - 10/30/2012 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - 10/1/2012 - 10/31/2012 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - 11/1/2012 - 11/29/2012 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - 11/1/2012 - 11/30/2012 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - 12/4/2012 - 12/21/2012 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 12/3/2012 - 12/20/2012 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 1/7/2013 - 1/28/2013 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 1/1/2013 - 1/31/2013 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 2/4/2013 - 2/27/2013 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 2/1/2013 - 2/28/2013 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 3/1/2013 - 3/29/2013 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 3/1/2013 - 3/20/2013 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - 4/4/2013 - 4/30/2013 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - 4/1/2013 - 4/26/2013 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 5/1/2013 - 5/30/2013 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - 5/3/2013 - 5/31/2013 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - 6/1/2013 - 6/20/2013 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - 6/3/2013 - 6/11/2013 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - 7/11/2013 - 7/31/2013 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - 7/10/2013 - 7/16/2013 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - 8/1/2013 - 8/28/2013 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - 8/5/2013 - 8/20/2013 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - 9/11/2013 - 9/27/2013 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - 9/16/2013 - 9/30/2013 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - 10/2/2013 - 10/31/2013 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - 10/1/2013 - 10/31/2013 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - 11/4/2013 - 11/25/2013 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - 11/4/2013 - 11/22/2013 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - 12/3/2013 - 12/18/2013 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - 12/2/2013 - 12/18/2013 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - 1/6/2014 - 1/29/2014 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 1/6/2014 - 1/29/2014 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 2/6/2014 - 2/26/2014 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 2/3/2014 - 2/27/2014 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 3/4/2014 - 3/31/2014 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - 3/3/2014 - 3/31/2014 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 4/1/2014 - 4/23/2014 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 4/1/2014 - 4/25/2014 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 5/8/2014 - 5/27/2014 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 5/5/2014 - 5/28/2014 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - 6/1/2014 - 6/25/2014 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - 6/3/2014 - 6/25/2014 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - 7/17/2014 - 7/31/2014 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - 7/17/2014 - 7/31/2014 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - 8/1/2014 - 8/27/2014 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - 8/18/2014 - 8/20/2014 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - 9/15/2014 - 9/29/2014 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - 9/11/2014 - 9/30/2014 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - 10/2/2014 - 10/30/2014 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - 10/1/2014 - 10/31/2014 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - 11/7/2014 - 11/23/2014 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - 11/3/2014 - 11/21/2014 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - 12/1/2014 - 12/18/2014 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - 12/1/2014 - 12/17/2014 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - 1/6/2015 - 1/30/2015 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - 1/5/2015 - 1/27/2015 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - 2/3/2015 - 2/24/2015 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - 2/2/2015 - 2/26/2015 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - 3/5/2015 - 3/31/2015 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - 3/2/2015 - 3/31/2015 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - 4/6/2015 - 4/27/2015 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - 4/1/2015 - 4/30/2015 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - 5/1/2015 - 5/26/2015 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 5/1/2015 - 5/29/2015 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 6/1/2015 - 6/24/2015 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 6/1/2015 - 6/23/2015 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 7/1/2015 - 7/29/2015 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 7/13/2015 - 7/23/2015 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - 8/1/2015 - 8/31/2015 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - 8/3/2015 - 8/27/2015 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - 9/1/2015 - 9/23/2015 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - 9/9/2015 - 9/30/2015 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - 10/1/2015 - 10/29/2015 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - 10/1/2015 - 10/30/2015 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - 11/1/2015 - 11/30/2015 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - 11/2/2015 - 11/30/2015 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - 12/1/2015 - 12/10/2015 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - 12/1/2015 - 12/15/2015 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - 1/4/2016 - 1/22/2016 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - 1/4/2016 - 1/29/2016 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - 2/2/2016 - 2/26/2016 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - 2/1/2016 - 2/19/2016 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - 3/1/2016 - 3/30/2016 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - 3/7/2016 - 3/30/2016 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - 4/1/2016 - 4/29/2016 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - 4/4/2016 - 4/28/2016 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - 5/4/2016 - 5/25/2016 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - 5/2/2016 - 5/27/2016 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - 6/1/2016 - 6/28/2016 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - 6/1/2016 - 6/21/2016 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - 7/12/2016 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - 7/25/2016 - 7/26/2016 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - 8/8/2016 - 8/31/2016 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - 8/23/2016 - 8/29/2016 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-015
  - A Celebration of John and Andrea Hennessy [DVD], 2016; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Videodisc 1U)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-027
  - "The Call of the West for Choir, Brass, and Percussion: Dedicated to John Hennessy, 10th President of Stanford University," Text by Jane Stanford; Music by Giancarlo Aquilanti, 2000 Sep (Box 1)
  - "Celebrating 10 Years -- John L. Hennessy: Master Builder," presented to John L. Hennessy on the occasion of the tenth anniversary of his presidency by the Board of Trustees, 2010 Oct 11 (Box 2)
    Scope and Contents
    Photographs of buildings erected on campus during Hennessy's first 10 years as President of Stanford University. Signed by several BOT members.
  - Photographs and Oversize Items from Hennessy's Presidential Office
    - Miscellaneous photographs and items from Hennessy's office (removed from frames) (Box 3)
    - Hennessy at Summit on Cyber Security and Consumer Protection with Barack Obama and Tim Cook, undated; SC0700_2017-027_01; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf10)
    - Hennessey speaking to audience, undated; SC0700_2017-027_02; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf10)
    - Hennessy at Founders Day with "Jane and Leland" in carriage, undated; SC0700_2017-027_03; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf10)
    - Hennessy reviewing computer printout, undated; SC0700_2017-027_04; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf10)
    - Hennessy hiking "Walk the Farm", undated; SC0700_2017-027_05; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf10)
    - Hennessy in meeting, undated; SC0700_2017-027_06; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf10)
    - Hennessy lecturing, undated; SC0700_2017-027_07; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf7)
    - Hennessy and his wife, Andrea, undated; SC0700_2017-027_08; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf7)
    - Hennessy speaking in academic regalia, undated; SC0700_2017-027_09; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf7)
    - Hennessy speaking, undated; SC0700_2017-027_10; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf7)
    - Hennessy with group applauding him, undated; SC0700_2017-027_11; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf7)
    - Hennessy with students on freshman move-in day, undated; SC0700_2017-027_12; 1 photograph(s) 24 x 36 inches (Map-case Sf7)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-123
  - Photographs (loose and in albums) and awards (Box 1)
  - Awards and scrapbook albums (Box 5)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-236
  - Invitation for dinner in honor of President John L. Hennessy and Mrs. Andrea Hennessy, 2016 Jun 8 (Box 1)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-269
  - Awards
    - IEEE Emanuel R. Piore Award Committee, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Society for Engineering Education LAMME Award, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - IEEE Fellow, 1991 Jan 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1996 Dec 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - IEEE Certificate of Appreciation, 1997 Aug 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - IEEE Service Award, 1997 Aug 25 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Gates Bldg, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ACM-IEEE Computer Society Eckert-Mauchly Award, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Materials
    Restricted for 20 years from date of creation.
    - Commission on Physical Sciences, Mathematics, and Applications, 1998 Oct 9-10 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Stanford University Flash Multiprocessor (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Task Force on Minority Alumni Relations, 1996 Oct (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Regis McKennain John Hennessey MIPS East Coast Tour R4000 Technology Announcement, 1991 Jan - Feb (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Computer Science and Telecommunications Board Meeting, 1998 Sep 17-18 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - School of Humanities and Sciences Board of Trustees, 1999 Jun (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter of the Parallel Processing Technical Committee volume 1 no. 2, 1993 Jan (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Proposal for Services Stanford University Information Sciences Facility, 1988 Mar 8 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Response to Architect's Questionnaire Information Sciences, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Sprankle, Lynd Sprague (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Information Sciences Project Stanford University (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Harry Weese Associates, 1988 Mar (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Architectural Services Proposal The Munselle Brown Partnership Inc., 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Stanford University Board of Trustees Agenda (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - To file - Miranda, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Information Technology Systems and Services, 1996 Oct 31 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Feasibility Study Center for Integrated Systems Office Addition, 1988 Feb (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Feasibility Study Center for Integrated Systems Office Addition, 1988 Feb (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Netpower (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-291
  - Hennessy Nation Reunion Block Party Ephemera, 2016 (Box 1)
- President's records, 2014-2015; Accession ARCH-2017-300
  - Emeriti, 7/9/2014 - 5/20/2015; AA 2_2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Development, 6/13/2014 - 5/15/2015; AA 2_7 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Education, 9/17/2014 - 8/1/2015; AA 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Accreditation Issues, 4/18/2014 - 4/21/2015; AA 3_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ratings/Rankings, 5/1/2014 - 5/11/2015; AA 3_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Online Learning, 5/8/2014 - 5/4/2015; AA 3_7_1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Summer Programs, 10/9/2014 - 5/27/2015; AA 3_16 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - School of Humanities Sciences, 10/31/2014 - 4/30/2015; AA 4_1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Economics, Dept. of, 2/14/2012 - 5/26/2015; AA 4_1_20 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - SIEPR, 12/9/2013 - 2/4/2015; AA 4_1_20_1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 10/2/2013 - 12/16/2014; AA 4_1_28 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Music, Dept. of, 11/19/2013 - 5/26/2015; AA 4_1_29 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Department of Athletics, 8/2/2001 - 8/12/2015; AA 4_1_30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Football Games, Rose Bowl, 9/11/2014 - 8/18/2015; AA 4_1_30_1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Political Science, Dept. of, 10/27/2014 - 12/17/2014; AA 4_1_34 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - GSB, 8/15/2000 - 6/1/2015; AA 4_2 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Earth Sciences, School of, 6/18/2012 - 3/4/2015; AA 4_3 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Engineering, School of, 11/13/2014 - 3/10/2015; AA 4_4 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Education, School of, 9/15/2000 - 2/16/2015; AA 4_5 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hoover Institution, 3/28/2001 - 7/28/2015; AA 4_9 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Stanford University Libraries, 5/11/2001 - 8/17/2015; AA 4_12 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Law School, 4/10/2001 - 4/3/2015; AA 4_15 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Awards Prizes (1 of 2), 9/10/2014 - 2/27/2015; AA 5 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Awards Prizes (2 of 2), 3/9/2015 - 8/27/2015; AA 5 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Grants Scholarships, 9/3/2014 - 8/31/2015; AA 6 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Fellowship, 4/17/2001 - 4/21/2015; AA 8_17 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, 6/30/2014 - 6/1/2015; AA 8_25 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Stanford Miscellaneous, 11/6/2003 - 7/8/2013; AD 1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Stanford Historical Society, 10/14/2013 - 2/11/2015; AD 1_2 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Reserve Officers' Training Corps (ROTC), 10/5/2011 - 6/8/2015; AD 2_26 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Judicial Affairs, 9/18/2014 - 8/31/2015; AD 3_10 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - President's Office, 7/19/2012 - 4/14/2015; AD 4 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Presidential Lectures Symposia, 9/25/2007 - 3/20/2015; AD 4_2 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, General, 10/25/2000 - 7/29/2015; AD 4_20 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Condolence Letters, 12/5/2013 - 5/15/2015; AD 4_20_2 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 11/1/2000 - 8/31/2015; AD 4_20_3 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Appreciation letters, 12/1/2000 - 8/27/2015; AD 4_20_4_1 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Invitations (1 of 4), 9/20/2000 - 12/16/2014; AD 4_20_4_2 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Invitations (2 of 4), 1/6/2015 - 4/28/2015; AD 4_20_4_2 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Invitations (3 of 4), 5/4/2015 - 6/29/2015; AD 4_20_4_2 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Invitations (4 of 4), 7/2/2015 - 8/31/2015; AD 4_20_4_2 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Holiday Cards, 12/19/2014 - 2/23/2015; AD 4_20_4_4 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Nonsense (1 of 3), 5/25/2001 - 1/27/2015; AD 4_20_5 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Nonsense (2 of 3), 2/9/2015 - 5/27/2015; AD 4_20_5 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Nonsense (3 of 3), 6/1/2015 - 8/26/2015; AD 4_20_5 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Recommendation Letters, 10/2/2014 - 5/24/2015; AD 4_20_6 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Solicitations (1 of 7), 9/13/2000 - 9/24/2014; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Solicitations (2 of 7), 10/2/2014 - 12/16/2014; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Solicitations (3 of 7), 1/6/2015 - 2/26/2015; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Solicitations (4 of 7), 3/4/2015 - 4/30/2015; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Solicitations (5 of 7), 5/1/2015 - 5/29/2015; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Solicitations (6 of 7), 6/1/2015 - 7/30/2015; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Solicitations (7 of 7), 8/3/2015 - 8/31/2015; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - University Communications, 9/18/2014 - 8/25/2015; AD 4_22 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Admissions (1 of 3), 6/6/2000 - 10/31/2014; AD 8_1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate Admissions (2 of 3), 11/4/2014 - 3/27/2015; AD 8_1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Admissions (3 of 3), 4/3/2015 - 8/31/2015; AD 8_1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Student Affairs, 10/16/2014 - 2/5/2015; AD 8_8 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bing Overseas Studies, 3/4/2015 - 5/1/2015; AD 8_11 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Financial Aid, 8/25/2000 - 8/24/2015; AD 8_12 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 7/16/2013 - 3/20/2015; AD 8_18 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Human Resources, 9/4/2014 - 8/11/2015; AD 10 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Emploment Inquiries, 9/3/2014 - 7/7/2015; AD 10_1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Events, Stanford and Public, 10/14/2013 - 8/5/2015; AD 11_7_5_1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Freshman Issues, 9/23/2012 - 5/20/2015; AD 11_7_7 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Media Publications, Misc., 9/26/2014 - 5/22/2015; AD 11_8 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Media Publications (internal), 9/4/2013 - 5/15/2015; AD 11_8_11 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Business Affairs, CFO, 9/15/2014 - 8/31/2015; AD 12_2 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Stanford Management Company, 6/4/2014 - 2/9/2015; AD 12_3 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Risk Management, 10/15/2014 - 8/24/2015; AD 12_8 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Office of Development, 9/19/2014 - 5/19/2015; AD 12_10_1 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - President's Fund, 3/3/2006 - 10/9/2012; AD 12_10_2_2 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - The Stanford Fund, 10/21/2014 - 8/25/2015; AD 12_10_2_3 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Asian Relations, 6/22/2012 - 7/14/2015; AD 12_10_2_9 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Land, Buildings, Real Estate, 5/19/1960 - 6/18/2015; AD 12_14 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - University Architect/Planning, 9/20/2005 - 1/10/2013; AD 12_14_7_29 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Jasper Ridge, 12/12/2006 - 2/24/2015; AD 12_14_7_43 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Parking Transportation, 3/21/2014 - 8/25/2015; AD 12_14_7_53 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, Misc., 1/1/2012 - 3/20/2015; AD 13_10_1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Relations, 11/3/2014 - 2/26/2015; AL 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Correspondence (1 of 2), 5/5/2000 - 12/17/2014; AL 1_3 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Correspondence (2 of 2), 1/14/2015 - 8/31/2015; AL 1_3 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Alumni Association, 10/16/2014 - 4/3/2015; AL 3 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees Committees, 6/18/2001 - 8/4/2015; B 14 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Land Building Campus Planning, BoT, 12/9/2013 - 10/13/2014; B 14_6 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Senate of the Academic Council, 12/5/2014 - 5/15/2015; C 2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - University Committees, 10/7/2013 - 5/15/2015; C 6 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Office of Government and Community Relations, 10/3/2014 - 7/23/2015; G 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - California State Government, 11/24/2014 - 7/21/2015; G 1_2 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - EPA, 9/18/2012 - 1/28/2015; G 2_3 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - United States Government Relations, 9/23/2014 - 6/30/2015; G 3 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Defense, Department of, 12/18/2013 - 6/30/2015; G 3_7 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Department of Education, 10/3/2014 - 8/27/2015; G 3_8_3 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 3/9/2007 - 7/14/2015; G 3_18_1 (Box 3, Folder 22)